it's
When you gotta play it smart
Not enough to chance the wise will take it all
Every I see the hell is the new toy
So I can't see the good that I'm good
Pan乱してく 運勢の thoughts
I'm 生んだ 支配し don't move
You're ready when all is good
You're ready it's gonna break
Da-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh
Good show to jede光 今すぐowie-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-h-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-h-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh-eh.
I had to to reign and彼 evident that you did it.
Oh!
Ah!
Oh...
left..
Oh, my gosh!
Thank goodness, I'm so worried about you!
Where am I?
Safe and sound at Sable's Inn.
To recap, you went unconscious on our way out.
That's really all there is to the recap.
Well, look who decided to wake up.
Thanks.
You didn't have to save me, but I'm glad that you did.
Dry your tears, little diaper baby.
We're moving out now.
You get to carry my stuff.
Huh?
They're supposed to be his allies, not his personal Sherpas.
Yay! I love toting things!
This'll be fun, Maz, right?
You know, this whole ordeal has taught me a very valuable lesson.
Our levels are leagues apart.
Anyone with eyes could see that.
That's why...
I want to meet your part-time apprentice!
While remaining a full-time bag boy, of course!
Please!
Just carry my things and don't embarrass me, or yourself.
Your benevolence knows no bounds!
Thank you for all your help, Seiya!
You idiot!
You referred to him as Master!
It doesn't matter what you're talking about.
Not my ideal kind of party, but I guess things could have turned out a lot worse.
This might seem kind of out of the blue, but there's a place I'd really like to take you to, Master.
Oh! I bet you're talking about Dragon's Den, aren't you?
Why would we go there?
According to Nagashi Village lore, 16 years ago, a dragon descended from the heavens carrying two babies, Elulu and myself.
Legend says we're to team up with a hero and defend Gea Bronde from a terrible evil.
It's said we need to break the seal in the dragon's den.
Only then will we be granted a mighty weapon to aid in our quest.
Huh?
Oh, Seiya loves a mighty weapon!
Yeah, but I'm already packing three enhanced platinum swords thanks to your premature balding issues.
We can discuss your hair hoarding later.
Besides, just when you think you have the very best, something even better comes along.
I think we should check this thing out for ourselves.
Forget it.
We need to make a major pit stop before we go anywhere.
You're kidding me. Seriously.
Whoa! We're really in the world where gods live?
Whoa! This is insane!
They have rings floating over their heads! Are they angels?
Would it be okay if we go exploring?
Don't be dumb. We came here to train.
I don't see him anywhere.
I think someone so big and bulky would be a lot easier to spot.
What's with the apron?
Care to tell us what the hell you're doing?
Oh, hey there, Seiya.
Not sure what business you could possibly have with a retired swordsman such as myself.
I mean, blades are dangerous.
There's a good chance I'd bleed out if I got caught.
The divine blade is afraid of swords now?
Great work, Seiya.
But, not to worry, I've been keeping busy by learning how to bake.
Here's a cake I just finished. You want a bite?
Nah, bro. That's gross.
How can you know without tasting?
I worked so hard on this.
I'll bet you'll have a bite.
A hard pass. It looks like it tastes like sweat and sad.
How would I even bake that?
I'm going to need you to focus.
Look, I didn't come here to dump on your lame hobbies.
Tell me, you still have your day job, don't you?
That should come first.
What's my day job?
This, obviously.
That's not my day job! It's a nightmare!
Get that thing away from me!
This guy seems a little unstable.
Relax, Pee Pants. I won't be the one you train this time around. He will.
Look at that. Seiya's almost being what some would call considerate.
I can't entrust my bags to a weakling.
My equipment would be ganked for sure.
Got yourself an apprentice, did you?
Mind if I see your abilities?
Sure, knock yourself out.
You weren't using that pesky fake-out skill just now, were you?
I'm afraid I wasn't.
Kid, you're in for some intense training!
I'll run you so hard your muscles will have muscles, little guy!
What is your deal, man? I think the chains on your mood swing just snapped!
Back to normal after he sees the outclass' mosh?
Man on the outside and fragile flower on the inside.
Sweet if it wasn't so sad.
So, you're asking me to teach this young one in the art of flame magic, correct?
I'd greatly appreciate it if you could.
It's our divine duty to support humans attempting to save their worlds.
I'd be delighted to help you.
Um, thank you. My name is Ailulu. It's an honor to make your acquaintance!
Such pretty red hair. Much like mine.
Let's try and calm those nerves down. Yes?
Okay, that takes care of those two.
All that's left to do now is to find someone who can train me.
I was wondering how long it'd take to bring it around back to him.
I'm so sorry!
Hey, Blondie!
You need to watch where you're walking.
Even a scrub goddess like you should be able to manage that.
Altery! Please forgive me! It won't ever happen again! You have my word!
That reminds me.
You got stuck bailing out a world with an S-class rank, didn't you?
That's pretty ambitious for someone who can't even put one foot in front of the other.
Well, you might have a point. I mean...
Good thing your bouncy plumpers more than make up for your faults.
And you've got some big faults.
Please stop! I'm not a piece of fruit, you know!
All right. I guess I'll let you off the hook.
But be more careful from now on.
I'm a little violated.
You get picked on in this world, huh?
I do not! Valkyrie just treats everyone like that!
I gotta say, I sense some serious power coming from that exhibitionist.
Please don't even think it. That was Valkyrie, the goddess of destruction.
She's the most fearsome goddess in the unified divine realm.
There's no way she'd train you.
For a human, talking to her is enough to risk instant annihilation.
Hey, Chainkini. Train me.
I know you're not talking to me in that tone.
The fact that you're a hero won't stop me from tearing you apart!
Yeah, I wish you would.
Please lock it up, Saiya!
How about you apologize and we can be on our way!
Apology? But what would be the point of that?
Since I'm gonna scatter his remains across the entire realm!
No! Have mercy!
Oh, pardon me!
Arya!
Valkyrie, please.
I bid you stand down and refrain from fighting.
As if I would!
This level of insolence deserves a punishment equal to a thousand deaths!
The mortal you keep threatening is a special hero who was summoned to save an S-class world in the utmost peril.
Please put your anger aside and let this man be.
In deference to myself, the high-ranking goddess Arya Doha.
Please, unhand him.
If you're gonna make a big scene about it, I'll let him go.
But in return, I get to give those chest muumus a nice massage sometime.
Uh, okay.
That was a whole new level of senseless, even for you!
Saiya, you really are something else.
Hey, I got a question.
Do you talk smack to everyone, or am I special?
I meant no offense.
So, rumor has it you're on the hunt for a new divine trainer.
I may know of a candidate if you're interested.
Meet the goddess of war, Adanella.
In terms of combat, she's a little more advanced than Circeus is.
Ah, it's nice to meet you, Adanella.
Well then, if you're not too busy, would you mind training up this hero?
D-train?
You want me to train a human?
You're kidding.
I'm gonna need to see some goddess ID because this girl is...
Disgusting. Disgusting as hell.
You're not supposed to say it out loud, even if we're all thinking it!
Hey, you know, I find some small joy in training.
Sure, I'll train the human.
I see you were able to follow my movements just now.
I wonder if your mind is as sharp as your sight.
Will you be able to learn what I have to teach and master the divine speed skill, Eternal Sword?
Or will your body give out and leave you sobbing like a spanked baby?
I did not sign up for this nightmare fuel.
Maybe we should look at other options.
Let's give it a shot.
Give it a what?!
How is this the one thing he's not cautious about?!
He made this Eternal Sword move sound pretty legit.
It's Eternal Sword, actually.
Blah, blah, blah. Let's do this.
I... I like your style.
Thanks, Aria. I'm in your debt again.
It's fine. I'm happy I could be of some help.
That's it. Now one more time.
Okay!
They're getting a lot better than I expected.
And I know I don't have to worry about Aylulu since she's with Hestika.
My only concern is getting this food to Seiya.
Huh? Shouldn't you be somewhere training a hero?
I'm... taking a break right now.
Seiya is still... practicing on his own, though.
How's he handling all that Eternal Sword stuff?
He's truly amazing.
Unlike any hero I've ever encountered before.
And... I think that...
You think what?
Nice! Let's dial back the freak face!
I... just remembered something that happened in training.
Seiya, he really amused me.
Hey, grunge bucket. Break's over. Let's go.
It's right. I'm on my way.
I forgot to give him his food!
I hope everyone's staying productive.
It's rare to see the pair of you share a meal in the cafeteria.
Shroomy here wanted some bro time.
I thought the least we could do was spin lunch together.
He's been teaching me all about the kind of mindset he has when he's in a fight.
Yeah. I'm kind of curious myself.
Not now. Dark and dingy's waiting on me.
Good talk! Thanks, Master!
Don't forget we're heading back to Gayabranday tomorrow!
So, what were you going to say about that fighting mindset stuff or whatever it was?
It more or less boiled down to doubt everyone and everything at all times.
Even your close friends and family members may be trying to kill you.
What a hysterical, paranoid, and delusional thing to fill an impressionable mind with.
Oh, there was another thing he said.
Remember, Mushroom, I suspect you just as much as everyone else.
Man, how cool is that?
Great. Now the universe has one more disciple of cautionism.
Is that you, Adanella?
It is! I don't believe it!
Kudos to whoever did your makeover!
Well, truth is, I was embarrassed by how I looked before.
I want to look nice for Saya.
Another enamored ditty bites the dust.
If he'd slay demon lords like he slays goddesses, we'd be set!
I hate to be a mother, but we're kind of on a time crunch.
Could my hero pick up your special skill at a later date?
The Eternal Sword? He mastered that technique already.
He what?
That human has a gift.
Yes, the size of which is truly something to behold and acknowledge.
And, best of all, he can.
Keep up with me!
I'm not sure why. She makes me even more uncomfortable now.
Thanks for everything!
No, I should be thanking you.
With your help, I managed to put that berserker nightmare behind me!
His level has risen dramatically.
Could Cersei actually be a half-decent teacher?
Hey, Alulu!
Oh, hi guys!
The hiatus is over!
So are you ready to go?
Because the sooner we head out, the better.
Um, right!
Hold on.
Our stats are basically the same as they were on day one!
Rista.
A word, if you will.
Look, let's be blunt.
Flame magic eludes that girl.
Oh, that can't be right.
She's trying her little heart out.
Magic depends largely upon the talent you're born with.
And sadly, that girl wasn't born with any talent at all.
Aww.
Seiya!
Can we finally go now?
Sure.
Once the creep queen shows, she said she had something she wanted to give me.
Seiya!
What the heck?
Hi, Seiya.
I've been doing some thinking, and I've decided to join your party.
You better be talking birthdays over there, because this party only has room for one goddess!
Well, if I can't be a teammate, then perhaps an escort?
I just want to be by your side.
It's love!
I'm in a moment!
Here.
This took me five hours to make.
I used my heart as the main ingredient.
Please, eat every bite.
Uh-oh, goth goddess has it bad.
Wait a sec.
Seiya hates cake.
Grossness.
Cake sucks.
Yes!
I called it!
Look, you're great at training, but you knew what this was.
It's not me, it's you.
And all cake can go straight to hell.
Period.
Sorry about you.
He really doesn't want it?
Hey, don't be so rude!
Jerk, don't you know love-struck girls are super fragile?
How about you just open the portal?
Hey, you too.
I better have all my stuff.
Cold front passing through.
Doorway to the other world open!
It's fine.
Please don't get mad!
Everything's fine.
You just don't want anything to do with me!
Just like you don't want anything to do with me!
She's way too powerful!
I am perfectly prepared.
I am 100% ready for this.
Seiya!
Now is not the time, okay?
You have an ETA for when we'll get to the dragon still?
Well, being a dragon kin lets me sense we're getting closer, so not far now.
Come on!
Whatcha up to back there, eh, Lulu?
Just practicing.
If a monster appears, I want to use my magic to help Seiya out.
I don't need your help.
You're a baggage handler.
So just handle my baggage.
Oh, okay.
Have you ever heard the phrase, kid gloves?
An orc!
Nice!
The chance to put all my training to the test!
Huh?
Oh!
The big bird came out of nowhere!
It literally beat me to the punch.
That is my automatic phoenix.
Meh.
This thing detects any monster within a 50-meter radius and automatically attacks it on sight.
Oh, that sounds like some stellar remote fire magic.
Yeah, leave it to you, master.
But I wouldn't mind taking out the next enemy.
Whoa!
Watch out!
Here comes a tree goblet!
Sweet!
Take that!
Fire arrow!
Rude!
Everything level 30 and under is killed instantly.
We can win without fighting.
There's no greater strategy than that.
He could at least let the kiddos feel like they're doing something useful.
But it's kind of comforting to know he's got another special skill under his belt.
Hmm.
That's the most obvious fake-out I've ever seen.
Nothing a little willpower can't change.
Time to unleash my amazing mega-miss power!
Huh?
What the heck is happening?
We're kind of cute in a weird way.
Hey!
Pull yourself together, Rista!
You're the absolute worst!
I thought you would have learned by now, but I'm not one to bro-and-tell.
Well, it's done like that again, and I'll destroy your head.
You do know we're on the same side, right?
Oh, you better not sneak a peek for a while.
Come on in!
We welcome you to Isalee Village.
Ah! Throttle back, Turbo!
They're just harmless dwarves.
They're classified as monsters, but most actually leave peaceful lives.
You sell torches, Bilbro Baggins?
Yes, we certainly do.
Are you going out to the dragon den, stranger?
So you've heard of it.
It's in the rocks out east, but the only thing you'll come across is a dead end.
That's it!
The entrance is sealed, but I bet a Lulu and I can fix that.
Hey, I've got a pop quiz for you.
How many torches will we need?
Hmm, 50 of them!
He's changed this poor boy's mind and corrupted his common sense.
Wrong.
We'll need 500 minimum.
They meant to say five!
She doesn't have any risk management skills.
Hey!
Reesey!
Look!
Mine too!
Must be close.
There!
That's it?
Good thing we didn't buy 499 more torches!
Forget that.
Check this.
Okay, Lulu.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Huh?
Uh, you good?
I'm lost.
What the crap are you doing?
By making my joints the paragon of flexibility, I'm able to repeat the actions of slicing, thrusting,
and sweeping at incredibly high speed.
This is the Eternal Sword, the chained attack blade!
Whoa, that attack demolished the seal!
I guess we really are useless after all.
No, you shouldn't feel that way.
Without you two, we would have never even found a seal to decimate!
Huh?
Okay!
So where's this big bad ultimate weapon hiding?
You've done well to come this far.
Welcome fellow descendants of the dragons.
What the?
Brave heroes, step into the magic circle.
It shall transport you to Dragon Village, where you will be given Exacean.
Exacean?
Is that how we're saying it?
Time to hop a ride on the glowy platform and get this adventure going!
It's kind of like a homecoming, isn't it, Elulu?
I might just die from the excitement!
Let's not do that, okay?
Okay, we're in the circle now.
Excellent!
Dragon Village awaits!
Uh, I think there were some technical difficulties.
We received a lizard.
Cool.
Nothing abnormal to make note of.
I am confident this is not a trap.
Welcome to Dragon Village.
Huh?
Your shocked response is only natural.
My people's dragonhood appearance is drastically different from that of the human race.
I am referred to as Lagos.
If you would be so kind as to follow me, I shall take you to our leader, Livae.
The village you see before you is a continent located far across the western sea.
Magic circles are the only means humans can travel here.
It seems young Mosh and Elulu have returned!
Mosh looks so dashing now that he's older.
Yes, and Elulu is simply adorable!
Say, if we're originally from here, why do we look so different from everyone else?
We dragon newts came into existence as children of both dragons and humans.
However, the more reptilian-seeming among us have more dragon blood in their veins.
So these guys look human because they got the weaker end of the DNA strand.
No.
Mosh and Elulu are choice individuals.
They are dragon kin who shoulder a tremendous destiny.
I'm pleased that both of you have safely returned to us.
Your companions are also welcome.
I am Livae, the reigning monarch and mother of Dragon Village.
Listen well.
The Demon Lord's conquest continues even as we speak.
Although the threat is imminent, you needn't worry.
You dragon kin have chosen the correct place to prepare.
Please step forward, young Mosh.
Me? For real?
Well?
I will show you how to transform into a dragon.
There.
By becoming a dragon newt, your abilities have improved considerably.
You look cool.
That's amazing.
Your ability ratings literally went up tenfold.
Yeah.
But you better keep your distance.
I can't promise I won't attack since you look like a monster.
That's so messed up!
On the plus side.
Now you can carry more of my equipment.
Ugh.
With proper training, you may one day transform from a dragon newt to a dragon god.
Then your skills will reach unparalleled heights.
Yeah!
That sounds good to me!
Um, your majesty, could you maybe show me how to transform too?
But why?
It serves you no purpose.
Oh, if you say so.
Worry not, child.
Your role in this endeavor will prove even greater than that of young Mosh.
Wow!
Do you really mean it?
Yes, my dear.
You are fated to become Exasian, the most powerful of weapons.
You will fulfill this destiny by offering up your life.
Huh?
Like, a sacrifice?
That's not okay.